African-American related sheet music, and sheet music written by African-Americans, 1851-1974 M1433
Stanford University. Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series II: Sheet Music with African-American themes
  - Oh Lucindy, Thekla Hollingsworth, Jessie L. Deppen, 1927 (Flat-box 6, Folder 7, Item 3)
  - Oh, That Moonlight Glide, Junie McCree, Albert Von Tilzer, 1910 (Flat-box 6, Folder 7, Item 4)
  - Oh! The Girl Upstairs, Dave Sonenscher, Julian Wright, 1925 (Flat-box 6, Folder 7, Item 5)
  - Old Black Joe, Louis A. Drumheller, 1906 (Flat-box 6, Folder 7, Item 6)
  - Old Black Joe, Stephen Foster, arr. E.G. Snelling, 1905 (Flat-box 6, Folder 7, Item 7)
  - Old Folks are Gone, G. Friedrich Wurzel, 1852 (Flat-box 6, Folder 7, Item 8)
  - Old Joe Blues, L. Wolfe Gilbert, Joe Samuels, Nat Vincent, 1919 (Flat-box 6, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - Old Joe's Dream, Brother Gardner, A. Alixa, 1890 (Flat-box 6, Folder 8, Item 2)
  - Old Love; Memphis Bound!, Don Walker, Clay Warnick, 1945 (Flat-box 6, Folder 8, Item 3)
  - Ole Sambo, A.J. Weidt, 1920 (Flat-box 6, Folder 8, Item 4)
  - Ole Shady or The Song of the Contraband, the author of "Darling Nelly Gray", 1861 (Flat-box 6, Folder 8, Item 5)
  - One Man Band, The, Ted Weems, Phil Baxter, 1931 (Flat-box 6, Folder 8, Item 6)
  - One Moment with You, Margaret Binney, A. Eileen Innes, 1932 (Flat-box 6, Folder 8, Item 7)
  - On the Good Ship Nancy Lee, Jack Yellen, George L. Cobb, 1913 (Flat-box 6, Folder 8, Item 8)
  - On the Hoko Moko Isle, Lou Klein, Harry Von Tilzer, 1916 (Flat-box 6, Folder 8, Item 9)
  - Oogie Oogie Wa Wa, Grant Clarke, Edgar Leslie, Archie Gottler, 1922 (Flat-box 6, Folder 8, Item 10)
  - Open Up Dem Pearly Gates, Carson J. Robison, 1932 (Flat-box 6, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Oriental Coon, The, Ed Rogers, 1899 (Flat-box 6, Folder 9, Item 2)
  - Pansy the Moon am Shining, Ed Rogers, 1909 (Flat-box 6, Folder 9, Item 3)
  - Parthenia to Ingomar, Wm. H. McCarthy, Stephen C. Foster, 1859 (Flat-box 6, Folder 9, Item 4)
  - Pendulum Song, The, Al Hoffman, John Murray, 1955 (Flat-box 6, Folder 9, Item 5)
  - Perfect Song, The; The Pepsodent Hour, Clarence Lucas, Joseph Carl Breil, 1940 (Flat-box 6, Folder 9, Item 6)
  - Phoebe Thompson's Cake Walk, Sadie Koninsky, 1899 (Flat-box 6, Folder 9, Item 7)
  - Piccaninnies, The; The Runaway Girl, Aubrey Hopwood, Ivan Caryll, 1897 (Flat-box 6, Folder 9, Item 8)
  - Pickaninnies on Parade, G.D. Barnard, 1897 (Flat-box 6, Folder 9, Item 9)
  - Plantation Medley, Paul Robertson, 1937 (Flat-box 6, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - Plantation Medley, A, J. Albert Snow, 1905 (Flat-box 6, Folder 10, Item 2)
  - Play that Barber Shop Chord, Wm. Tracey, Lewis F. Muir, 1910 (Flat-box 6, Folder 10, Item 3)
  - 'Pon My Soul, Dave Hogg, Maury Longfellow, 1933 (Flat-box 6, Folder 10, Item 4)
  - Poor Aunt Dinah, "Composed by the author", 1850 (Flat-box 6, Folder 10, Item 5)
  - Poverty Rag, Harry J. Lincoln, 1909 (Flat-box 6, Folder 10, Item 6)
  - Pray for the Lights to Go Out, Renton Tunnah, Will E. Skidmore, 1916 (Flat-box 6, Folder 10, Item 7)
  - Pretty Little Dinah Jones, J.B. Mullen, 1902 (Flat-box 6, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - Princess Zulu Lulu, Dave Reed, Jr., 1902 (Flat-box 6, Folder 11, Item 2)
  - Prohibition Blues, AL. Sweet, 1918 (Flat-box 6, Folder 11, Item 3)
  - Quit Cryin' the Blues, Felix Lewis, 1931 (Flat-box 6, Folder 11, Item 4)
  - Ragtime Eyes, W.C. Powell, 1907 (Flat-box 6, Folder 11, Item 5)
  - Ragtime Mose's Oldtime Bomboshay, Gus Van, Joe Schenck, Malvin M. Franklin, 1918 (Flat-box 6, Folder 11, Item 6)
  - Rastus Thompson's Rag-Time Cake Walk, Andrew B. Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer, 1898 (Flat-box 6, Folder 11, Item 7)
  - Razors in the Air, Barry Maxwell, 1880 (Flat-box 7, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Rememb'ring; Topsy And Eva, Duncan Sisters, 1923 (Flat-box 7, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - Riverside Rag, Chas. Cohen, 1910 (Flat-box 7, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - River, Stay 'Way from My Door, Mort Dixon, Harry Woods, 1931 (Flat-box 7, Folder 1, Item 4)
  - Rockin' Chair Swing, Vincent Lopez, Mary Schaeffer, 1937 (Flat-box 7, Folder 1, Item 5)
  - Rusty Old Halo, A, Bob Merrill, 1955 (Flat-box 7, Folder 1, Item 6)
  - Sam's Laugh, Ed O'Connor, 1905 (Flat-box 7, Folder 1, Item 7)
  - Sand Man's Song, The, Mortimer Furchgott, 1900 (Flat-box 7, Folder 1, Item 8)
  - Satisfied, Theron C. Bennett, 1904 (Flat-box 7, Folder 1, Item 9)
  - Save a Little Dram for Me, Will E. Skidmore, Marshall Walker, 1920 (Flat-box 7, Folder 1, Item 10)
  - Say You Love Me Sue, Harry B. Smith, John Stromberg, 1899 (Flat-box 7, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Sensitive Coon, The, Pedro A. Andreu, 1851 (Flat-box 7, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Shake Rattle and Roll, Charles Calhoun, 1954 (Flat-box 7, Folder 2, Item 3)
  - Shaky Eyes, Billy Clark, Harry Armstrong, 1909 (Flat-box 7, Folder 2, Item 4)
  - She's Tall, She's Tan, She's Terrific; 3rd Edition Cotton Club Parade, Benny Davis, J. Fred Coots, 1937 (Flat-box 7, Folder 2, Item 5)
  - She's the Real Thing My Baby, Theo. A. Northrop, 1901 (Flat-box 7, Folder 2, Item 6)
  - Shew Fly!, Billy Reeves, Frank Campbell, arr. Rollin Howard, 1869 (Flat-box 7, Folder 2, Item 7)
  - Shine on Mister Moon, Robert M. Stults, 1910 (Flat-box 7, Folder 2, Item 8)
  - Shoe-Shine Boy, Sammy Cahn, Saul Chaplin, 1936 (Flat-box 7, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Shoo Shoo Boogie Boo, Leo Robin, Sam Coslow, Richard A. Whiting, 1929 (Flat-box 7, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Show the Whites Of Yo' Eyes, Stanley Crawford, 1903 (Flat-box 7, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - Silhouettes, Frank C. Slay, Jr., Bob Crewe, 1957 (Flat-box 7, Folder 3, Item 4)
  - Slavery's Passed Away, Edward Harrigan, Dave Braham, 1888 (Flat-box 7, Folder 3, Item 5)
  - Smoky Mokes, A. Holzmann, 1899 (Flat-box 7, Folder 3, Item 6)
  - Sneeky Peet, Chas. L. Johnson, 1907 (Flat-box 7, Folder 3, Item 7)
  - So a Congo Neger Hat's Halt Guat!, Wilh. Wiesberg, Joh. Sioly, no date (Flat-box 7, Folder 3, Item 8)
  - Society Swells, J. Lawrence Ritchie, 1903 (Flat-box 7, Folder 3, Item 9)
  - Soldier Boy from Caroline, Jake Mahoney, 1942 (Flat-box 7, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Somebody's Been Around Here Since I've Been Gone, John W. Bratton, Paul West, 1907 (Flat-box 7, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - Song of the Bayou, Rube Bloom, 1929 (Flat-box 7, Folder 4, Item 3)
  - Southern Hospitality, Arthur Pryor, 1899 (Flat-box 7, Folder 4, Item 4)
  - Southern Jollification, Charles Kunkel, 1890 (Flat-box 7, Folder 4, Item 5)
  - Stay in Your Own Backyard, Karl Kennett, Lyn Udall, 1899 (Flat-box 7, Folder 4, Item 6)
  - Stormy Weather; 22nd Edition Cotton Club Parade, Ted Koehler, Harold Arlen, 1933 (Flat-box 7, Folder 4, Item 7)
  - Sugar Moon, Stanley Murphy, Percy Wenrich, 1910 (Flat-box 7, Folder 4, Item 8)
  - Summertime; Porgy And Bess, DuBose Heyward, George Gershwin, 1935 (Flat-box 7, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Summer Time in Dixie, Hattie Nevada, 1899 (Flat-box 7, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - Sunbeam Sue, Robert A. Keiser, 1900 (Flat-box 7, Folder 5, Item 3)
  - Swanee Rag, Chas. L. Johnson, 1912 (Flat-box 7, Folder 5, Item 4)
  - Sweet Miss Mary, W.H. Neidlinger, 1906 (Flat-box 7, Folder 5, Item 5)
  - Sympathy, Kendis and Paley, 1905 (Flat-box 7, Folder 5, Item 6)
  - 'Taint So, Honey, 'Taint So, Willard Robison, 1928 (Flat-box 7, Folder 5, Item 7)
  - Taking a Chance on Love; Cabin in the Sky, John Latouche, Ted Fetter, Vernon Duke, 1942 (Flat-box 7, Folder 5, Item 8)
  - Tar and Cement, Paul Vance, Lee Pockriss, L. Beretta, M. Del Prete, A. Celentano, 1966 (Flat-box 7, Folder 5, Item 9)
  - That Brass Band Rag, R.G. Grady, 1912 (Flat-box 7, Folder 5, Item 10)
  - That Ragtime Harmony Strain, 1914 (Flat-box 7, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - That's the Way It is, Joan Whitney, Alex Kramer, 1945 (Flat-box 7, Folder 6, Item 2)
  - That's Why Darkies were Born, Lew Brown, Ray Henderson, 1931 (Flat-box 7, Folder 6, Item 3)
  - That Yoddlin' Zulu Rag, J. Brandon Walsh, Al. W. Brown, 1910 (Flat-box 7, Folder 6, Item 4)
  - They made It Twice as Nice As Paradise and They Called It Dixieland, Raymond Egan, Richard A. Whiting, 1916 (Flat-box 7, Folder 6, Item 5)
  - Things Ain't the Same, Babe, I'm Coming Home, Will Tobias, Will Hamer, 1902 (Flat-box 7, Folder 6, Item 6)
  - Three Little Words; Check and Double Check, Bert Kalmar, Harry Ruby, 1930 (Flat-box 7, Folder 6, Item 7)
  - Tickled to Death, Chas. Hunter, 1899 (Flat-box 7, Folder 6, Item 8)
  - Time to Go, Sid Frank, Ray Getzov, Yvon Alain, Eddy Marnay, 1952 (Flat-box 7, Folder 6, Item 9)
  - Tomorrow is Another Day, Bud Green, Sam H. Stept, 1930 (Flat-box 7, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Too Tired, Geo. A. Little, Arthur Sizemore, Larry Shay, 1924 (Flat-box 7, Folder 7, Item 2)
  - Trabble on, Thorvald Otterstrom, 1917 (Flat-box 7, Folder 7, Item 3)
  - Turkey in the Straw, Otto Bonnell, 1904 (Flat-box 7, Folder 7, Item 4)
  - Underneath the Harlem Moon, Mach Gordon, Harry Revel, 1932 (Flat-box 7, Folder 7, Item 5)
  - Under the Bridges of Paris, Dorcas Cochran, J. Rodor, Vincent Scotto, 1953 (Flat-box 7, Folder 7, Item 6)
  - Under the Tropical Moon, C.P. McDonald, Percy Wenrich, 1907 (Flat-box 7, Folder 7, Item 7)
  - Up In a Cocoanut Tree, Edward Madden, Theodore Morse, 1903 (Flat-box 7, Folder 7, Item 8)
  - Virginia Rag, Sydney P. Harris, 1907 (Flat-box 7, Folder 7, Item 9)
  - Wait for the Wagon, Geo. P. Knauff, 1851 (Flat-box 7, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - Warmest Baby in the Bunch, The, Geo. M. Cohan, 1897 (Flat-box 7, Folder 8, Item 2)
  - Warmin' Up In Dixie, A, E.T. Paull, 1899 (Flat-box 7, Folder 8, Item 3)
  - Way Down In Dear Old Alabama, Frank Dupree, J.W. Wheeler, 1900 (Flat-box 7, Folder 8, Item 4)
  - Weaving Around Rag, Lawrence Mitchel, 1913 (Flat-box 7, Folder 8, Item 5)
  - Wee Wee Negro Caprice, Victor E. Hammerel, 1877 (Flat-box 7, Folder 8, Item 6)
  - What a Wonderful World, George David Weiss, George Douglas, 1967 (Flat-box 7, Folder 8, Item 7)
  - What You Goin' to Do When the Rent Comes 'Round?, Andrew B. Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer, 1905 (Flat-box 7, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - When Chloe Sings a Song, Harry B. Smith, John Stromberg, 1899 (Flat-box 7, Folder 9, Item 2)
  - When I Gets Out in No-Man's Land, Will E. Skidmore, Marshall Walker, 1918 (Flat-box 7, Folder 9, Item 3)
  - When I Hear That "Jaz" Band Play, Jerry Joyce, Eddie Gray, 1916 (Flat-box 7, Folder 9, Item 4)
  - When It's Moon Light on the Levee, Caroline, Richard H. Gerard, George Evans, 1903 (Flat-box 7, Folder 9, Item 5)
  - When It's Night Time Down in Dixieland, Irving Berlin, 1914 (Flat-box 7, Folder 9, Item 6)
  - When Mr. Shakespeare Comes to Town, Wm. Jerome, Eugene Black, 1901 (Flat-box 7, Folder 9, Item 7)
  - When My Dark Diana Dreams of Me, Earle C. Jones, Charles N. Daniels, 1911 (Flat-box 7, Folder 9, Item 8)
  - When Old Bill Bailey Plays the Ukalele, Chas. McCarron, Nat. Vincent, 1915 (Flat-box 7, Folder 9, Item 9)
  - When Uncle Joe Plays a Rag on His Old Banjo, D.A. Esrom, Theodore Morse, 1912 (Flat-box 7, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - When Uncle Joe Steps Into France, Bernie Grossman, Billy Winkle, 1918 (Flat-box 7, Folder 10, Item 2)
  - Without a Song, William Rose, Edward Eliscu, Vincent Youmans, 1932 (Flat-box 7, Folder 10, Item 3)
  - Won't You Let Me Put My Arms Around You or That Certainly Am "Zulu Love", Bob Adams, 1906 (Flat-box 7, Folder 10, Item 4)
  - Won't You Roll Dem Eyes, Andrew B. Sterling, Harry Von Tilzer, 1902 (Flat-box 7, Folder 10, Item 5)
  - Won't You Throw a Kiss to Me, Wm. McKenna, 1906 (Flat-box 7, Folder 10, Item 6)
  - You Got to Play Rag Time, Jean C. Havez, A.B. Sloane, 1899 (Flat-box 7, Folder 10, Item 7)
  - You'll Never Miss the Water Till the Well Runs Dry, Frank W. Sterns, Ernest S. Erdman, 1905 (Flat-box 7, Folder 10, Item 8)
  - You Went Away Too Far and Stayed Away Too Long, Alfred Bryan, James V. Monaco, 1926 (Flat-box 7, Folder 10, Item 9)
  - Zambesi Dance, C. H. Borel-Clerc, 1914 (Flat-box 7, Folder 10, Item 10)
  - Zip-a-Dee-Doo-Dah; Song of the South, Allie Wrubel, Ray Gilbert, 1946 (Flat-box 7, Folder 10, Item 11)